allmerchants.com 2015-12-29

# Privacy Policy

AllMerchants L.L.C ("AllMerchants") takes your privacy and security very seriously. In order to demonstrate our firm commitment to you, our website patrons and customers, we'd like to share our policies on information gathering, privacy, security, unsolicited email, returns and more...

**1\. Your Personal Information:** This site may utilize forms for information requests and orders. Contact information from all forms (including name, address, email address, payment info, shipping info, etc.) is used to process information requests and deliver orders. At no time will we share any of this information with any other person or company unless: We have your consent to share the information; We need to share the information to provide the product or service you have requested; We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of AllMerchants to provide a product or service to you.; or We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process. Any financial information our customers submit, such as credit card number and expiration date is used _only_ to charge the customer for what they are purchasing.

**2\. Security:** This site has extensive security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All orders are processed using SSL technology via a secure server. All customer contact information including credit card number, name and address are guarded with the utmost security and discretion. We restrict access to your nonpublic personal information to those employees who reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you. 

**3\. Unsolicited email:** We do ****_not_ **** use, nor do we condone the use of unsolicited bulk email. Validated complaints against our affiliates result in cancellation of their account(s). We take this issue very seriously. Please contact us to report any incidents of unsolicited email coming from or mentioning AllMerchants. All matters will be investigated and dealt with promptly. 

**4.** **Subscribe/Unsubscribe:** We offer free e-newsletters and mailing-lists to our visitors. We never rent these opt-in list of email addresses. We may however, offer sponsorship advertising and/or send special alerts and sale announcements to our subscribers from time to time. Subscribers may opt-out of receiving any future messages by taking the appropriate actions to unsubscribe at any time.

**5\. Cookies:** A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. This site may use cookies to ensure proper commission tracking for our affiliates, special popup window tracking, sign in identification, personal preferences tracking, and tracking of shopping cart items while you are using AllMerchants services. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.) If you reject all cookies, you may not be able to fully utilize all AllMerchants products or services. 

**6\. Server Logs:** AllMerchants automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address and the page you requested.

**7\. Advertisements:** AllMerchants sometimes displays targeted advertisements that may be of interest or benefit to you based on nonpublic personal information. If you respond to these advertisements and then give the advertiser personal information about yourself, you may reveal to the advertiser or ad server that you possess the characteristics used to select the audience for the advertisement. AllMerchants does not share any personally identifiable information about you with any third parties when you click on these ads. If you do not wish to disclose information about yourself to advertisers, you may choose to communicate with the advertiser directly in a manner that does not disclose that you viewed the AllMerchants advertisement.

**8\. Web Beacons:** Web pages may contain electronic images (called a "single-pixel GIF" or "web beacon") that allow a web site to count users who have visited that page or to access certain cookies. In general, any electronic image viewed as part of a web page, including an ad banner, can act as a web beacon. Advertising networks that serve ads onto AllMerchants may use web beacons in their advertisements. AllMerchants sometimes uses web beacons in HTML-formatted email messages (messages that include graphics) that AllMerchants itself sends in order to determine which email messages were opened and to note whether a message was acted upon.

**9\. Questions or Suggestions:** If you have any questions about this statement, the practices of this website, or your dealings with AllMerchants, please contact us.
